[{"question": " hey! i just got uh, my teacher evaluations! check out what this one student wrote, &quot;i loved dr. geller&#146;s class. mind blowing lectures! dr. geller, you are definitely the hottie of the paleontology department!&quot;", "answer": " ahh, hotties of the paleontology department, there&#146;s a big selling calendar, eh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " who wrote it?", "answer": " oh, i wish i knew, but the evaluations are all anonymous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " oh hey, do you still have their final exams?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " a hot girl&#146;s at stake and all of the sudden he&#146;s rain man.", "answer": " okay, wait a minute, wait a minute, why are we so sure that this is a girl?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " it&#146;s a girl! anyway, it wou&#151;it wouldn&#146;t matter. okay? because i&#146;m a teacher and she&#146;s a student.", "answer": " oh, is that against the rules?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " no, but it is frowned upon.", "answer": " i see.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " besides, there&#146;s a big age difference.", "answer": " oh, well think of it like this, when you&#146;re 90&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " i know when i&#146;m 90 she&#146;ll be like 80 and it won&#146;t seem like such a big difference.", "answer": " no that&#146;s not what i was going to say at all. no, what i was going to say is when you&#146;re 90 you&#146;ll still have the memory of what it was like to be with a 20-year-old.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " hey chandler! y&#146;know that girl you went to college with who-who became a movie director?", "answer": " oh yeah, dana keystone. she was in my movement class.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " what&#146;s a movement class?", "answer": " it&#146;s chandler&#146;s way of pretending he didn&#146;t take mime.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " oh well listen, anyway she&#146;s directing the new al pacino movie. you gotta get me an audition!", "answer": " oh, i don&#146;t know man. i haven&#146;t talked to her in like ten years.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " no-no-no, please-please chandler i-i-i would owe you so much!", "answer": " you do owe me so much. you owe me three thousand, four hundred&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " hey-hey dude, why are you changing the subject? why? will you make the call or what?", "answer": " oh okay, i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll try.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " all right! thanks! you&#146;re the best! now listen, the last day of auditions is thursday. okay? so i gotta get in there by thursday. okay? just remember thursday. thursday. can you remember thursday?", "answer": " yeah so, tuesday?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  thursday! look if you need help remembering think of like this, the third day. all right? monday, one day. tuesday, two day. wednesday, when? huh? what day? thursday! the third day! okay?!", "answer": "  thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": "  hey mon? i&#146;m gonna check my messages.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " you just thought of that in there?", "answer": " yeah sure, nature called, she wanted to see who else did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  hello?  uh, rachel.  great, someone is in our apartment. call the cops!", "answer": " you&#146;re on the phone!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  oh my god! oh my god! thank you!  that was the fire department, there was a fire at our place!", "answer": " oh my god! how bad was it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " well, he didn&#146;t say, but it was a fire. i&#146;m guessing not very good. come on, we gotta go!", "answer": " come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " what are you smiling about? what is so funny?", "answer": " the part i want to audition for is a fireman, this is so meant to be!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " professor geller?", "answer": "  yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i wanted to say how much i enjoyed your class.", "answer": " oh thank you. thanks very much.  ow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " uh, i&#146;m a little embarrassed about calling you a hottie on my evaluation&#133;", "answer": " that was you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " yeah. i felt a little weird about it. you&#146;re a teacher. i&#146;m a student. but would you maybe want to go out with me sometime?", "answer": " oh i, i don&#146;t-i don&#146;t think that would be the best idea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh, because i was thinking, the semester&#146;s over; you&#146;re not my teacher anymore.", "answer": " what time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": "  oh, y&#146;know what? forget it, you already gave me an a.", "answer": " gotcha.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " i&#146;m kidding!", "answer": " oh! so-so seriously, what time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh well, it&#146;s not so bad.", "answer": " yeah, most of the damage is pretty mostly contained in the bedrooms.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": "  hey buddy, do you think i can borrow your uniform this thursday?", "answer": " excuse me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " oh, how bad is it?", "answer": " oh, it&#146;s bad. it&#146;s really bad. the only thing in there that isn&#146;t burned is an ass. which i do not remember buying!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " how&#146;s your room rach?", "answer": " everything&#146;s ruined. my bed. my clothes. look at my favorite blue sweater.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " isn&#146;t that mine?", "answer": " fine! i&#146;m sorry for your loss!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " so uh, you&#146;re not gonna be able to live here for a while, you ladies have a place to stay?", "answer": "  wow! oh-okay, look pal, i am not in the mood to be hit on right now! but if you give me your number i will call you some other time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": "  yes, they can stay with us.", "answer": " have you figured out what started the fire mr. fireman?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " well uh, do either of you smoke?", "answer": " no, not usually. but yeah, i could use one right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " no-no-no, do you uh light candles? burn incense?", "answer": " yes! i do! all the time! i love them! oh my god! i did it! it&#146;s me! it&#146;s me! i burned down the house! i burned down the house!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " god, it&#146;s great to catch up! i can&#146;t believe how long it&#146;s been!", "answer": " chandler, is that&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  oh that&#146;s great! good for you.", "answer": " hey-hey listen&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " okay! so yeah, maybe we can get together umm&#133;  can you hold for one second please?  what?!", "answer": " when you&#146;re off the phone, do you wanna get a pizza?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  we didn&#146;t get to the audition. i&#146;m gonna take her to coffee and then we&#146;ll do it then.", "answer": " ah-ha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " wow! so, now you&#146;re going on a date with this girl?", "answer": " honey, it is not a date! i haven&#146;t talked to her in ten years! you can&#146;t just call up somebody you haven&#146;t talked to in ten years and ask them for a favor. there are rules, y&#146;know? you gotta, you got to put in some time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " you&#146;re right, i&#146;m sorry. it&#146;s not like you&#146;re y&#146;know, going out with an ex-girlfriend.", "answer": " no, we only went out once.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " you dated her!", "answer": " not once!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " all right, well why don&#146;t i go out with an ex-boyfriend and do joey a favor?!", "answer": " hey, you wanna do joey a favor, maybe you go out with joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": "  oh that&#146;s great, my friend joey&#146;s in the movie business.", "answer": " y&#146;know who i ran into from school? howie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": "  my friend&#146;s name is joey.", "answer": " apparently howie&#146;s editing now. yeah, he-he-he calls me up and asks me if he can edit my new movie. can you believe that?! y&#146;know i-i-i haven&#146;t spoken to him in like ten years and he asks me for a favor!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " yeah, i&#146;ve always hated that howie.", "answer": " no, no &quot;how you doing?&quot; man, i mean not even a cup of coffee first!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " the nerve huh?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " oh my god! it sure didn&#146;t look this way when i lived here.", "answer": " i know! now look, there&#146;s only one problem though. there&#146;s only room for one, so i guess one of you will have to stay at joey&#146;s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " well, since the fire was kinda my fault i guess  you should get to stay here.", "answer": " hey! hey-hey, now this was no one&#146;s fault pheebs. okay? it was an accident.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " well no, it was my fault so you should get the nice room.", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " so rach! you&#146;re the first guest at hotel monica! umm, you&#146;ll just have to tell me how you like your eggs in the morning. and i thought i would bring them to you, y&#146;know, in bed. oh, you have been through so much.", "answer": " i have.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " what&#146;s that smell?", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " oh please! it was such a big class! you never even noticed me!", "answer": " what? of course i did! you uh, you sat next to sleepy sleeperson.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " who?", "answer": " oh uh, i had trouble remembering everyone&#146;s name, so i-i kinda came up with nicknames. like the guy on the other side of you was smelly von brownshirt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh yeah. so umm, did you have a nickname for me?", "answer": " umm, no. no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " yes you did! what was it?", "answer": " umm, it&#146;s cutie mcpretty.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " ohh that&#146;s so sweet!", "answer": " listen, i gotta tell ya, i-i&#146;m having a great time! y&#146;know how before you said it might be weird, the whole student teacher thing, and to be frank i thought it would be too, but it&#146;s not. i mean it&#146;s not at all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  dr. geller!", "answer": "  burt!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " so did you sleep well last night?", "answer": " i did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " i did, monica was so sweet she left a little mint on my pillow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " y&#146;know what joey left on my pillow?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " gum!", "answer": " well, we determined the cause of the fire.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " yeah i know, it was my candle. my candle!", "answer": " no, there was an appliance left on in the bathroom. it&#146;s looks like a curling iron.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i don&#146;t use a curling iron.", "answer": " well someone does.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " well, don&#146;t look at me! my hair&#146;s straight! straight! straight! straight!", "answer": " it could&#146;ve been a hair straightener.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " now there you go! i wouldn&#146;t want my best guest to strain her eyes!", "answer": " thanks monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " does that smell bother you?", "answer": " what the smell from joey&#146;s? no, i can hardly smell it over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " well you let me know if you can, because y&#146;know i can bake a pie to cover it.", "answer": " i can smell it a little, bake the pie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " hello?  oh yes, one minute please.  it&#146;s for you. it&#146;s the fire inspector.", "answer": " oh!  hello?  yeah this is phoebe.  really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " we had such a great time! she&#146;s-she&#146;s incredible! i thought the-the age difference might be a problem, but it wasn&#146;t. it wasn&#146;t at all. elizabeth is very mature for her age.   a concept lost on some people!", "answer": " so it&#146;s okay to date a student.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " well, not really. i mean technically it&#146;s-it&#146;s not against the rules or anything, but it is frowned upon. especially by that professor we ran into last night, judgey von holierthanthou.", "answer": " well ross, you be careful now. you don&#146;t want to get a reputation as y&#146;know professor mcnailshisstudents.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " yeah. what-what should i do?", "answer": " well ross, it seems pretty clear. i mean what&#146;s more important? what people think or how you feel, huh? ross, you gotta follow your heart.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey-hey-hey! so, how did it go with dana? any reason i should leave a block of time open say thursday?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " i couldn&#146;t do it.", "answer": " you couldn&#146;t do it?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hey, relax i just need more time. we&#146;re going to dinner tonight.", "answer": " what?! you&#146;re going out with her again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " going out with who?", "answer": " uh, dana keystone from college.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " no, that was dana caplin.", "answer": " ohhhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " joey! you didn&#146;t even know her!", "answer": " ah whatever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " great story again! the yarns that you weave! woo-hoo-hoo!", "answer": " y&#146;know uh, actually i-i-i should get going.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " oh no-no-no! stay! stay! because you-you should you-you-you should stay!", "answer": " wow. oh, i am really flattered, but i just i don&#146;t feel that way about you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " oh no-no-no, that&#146;s not&#151;no-no-no!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry chandler, y&#146;know you are such a sweet guy and i, i don&#146;t want to hurt you. oh, i wish there was something i can do to make you feel better.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " no-no&#151;really?!", "answer": " of course!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  well, it just hurts so bad. i uh&#133;", "answer": " ohh, i&#146;m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " well maybe there is one thing you can do.", "answer": " what?! anything! anything!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " well, i umm, i mean this is just off the top of my head now, umm but i have this friend. this actor friend and he would kill me if he thought i was doing this umm, but umm would it be possible for him to get an audition for your movie say on thursday?", "answer": " absolutely! but you-you would really feel better about me rejecting you if your actor friend can audition for my movie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " hey! how&#146;s it goin&#146;?", "answer": " well, not much has changed in the last five minutes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " yes it has! i made cookies!", "answer": " oh that&#146;s all right. i&#146;m still full from your homemade potato chips.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " but you should eat them now because they&#146;re hot from the oven.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": "  oh-ho! but not in here! can&#146;t eat &#145;em in bed, remember? no crumbies!", "answer": "  okay, i&#146;ll be out in a second.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": "  what are you doing?", "answer": " that doesn&#146;t lock does it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " oh, joey! sorry!", "answer": " no that&#146;s all right. don&#146;t worry about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " oh but look! that&#146;s gonna leave a stain!", "answer": " rach! hey! it&#146;s fine! you&#146;re at joey&#146;s!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah! look!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i&#146;ve never lived like this before.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " what do you want to do now? huh? you wanna go get a drink?", "answer": " uhh, i can&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " oh, you have some studying to do?", "answer": " no, i have some turning 21 to do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " nothing, i&#146;m-i&#146;m just, i&#146;m so comfortable with you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " do you not want to be seen with me?", "answer": " what? no! of course, of course i do! are-are they gone?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " uh no, they&#146;re still here but i think i&#146;m about to leave.", "answer": " what?! no! no! wait! you&#146;re right, this is stupid. who cares what people think? i mean, i mean we like each other right? there&#146;s nothing wrong with that. come on.  burt? lydia? mel? this is elizabeth.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " aren&#146;t you in my popular culture class?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " that&#146;s right lydia, elizabeth here is a student and uh, we&#146;re dating. and you may frown upon that, but we&#146;re not gonna hide it anymore.", "answer": " you are so fired.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " they&#146;re gonna fire you! you can&#146;t date a student! it&#146;s against the rules.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " i love it at joey&#146;s!", "answer": " hey, here you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": "  ni-hi-ice!", "answer": " thanks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": "  so, you busy thursday?", "answer": " oh, very funny. i don&#146;t know if you remember, but my audition was supposed to be thursday.  you got me the audition?! let&#146;s hug it up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " okay. okay.  what are you gonna do to me if you get the part?", "answer": "  hey! hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": "  listen umm, yeah okay, i need to talk to you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " now i know that they said that the umm, the hair straightener started the fire but i think i&#146;m partly at fault. you see, i didn&#146;t, i didn&#146;t tell you but umm, but i-i had recently refilled the tissues and so y&#146;know let&#146;s just face it, that&#146;s just kindling! so i think it&#146;s better that i stay at joey&#146;s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " no, no-no-no. phoebe, this was my fault and besides y&#146;know what? i&#146;m fine here.", "answer": " okay. oh umm, chandler, monica is looking for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah she said something about crumbies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": "  okay, you have to switch with me! monica is driving me crazy!", "answer": " that&#146;s right, all the ladies want to stay at joey&#146;s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " no! no! phoebe, come on! i don&#146;t want to switch! please come on! i can throw wet paper towels here!", "answer": " no but at monica&#146;s you can eat cookies over the sink!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " i know. i&#146;m sorry.", "answer": " all right fine! this looks like so much fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " god, what a mess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " wow! it actually is in the handbook. i can&#146;t date you or have a hot plate in my office. i can&#146;t believe we have to stop seeing each other.", "answer": " for what it&#146;s worth i did appreciate you standing up for me. it felt really nice. it kinda made me like you even more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " i know, i know i really like you too. but we-we can&#146;t date. it&#146;s against the rules. it&#146;s forbidden.", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " just hearing you describe it as forbidden, it&#146;s really hot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " well i-i-i don&#146;t care how hot it is it&#146;s-it&#146;s uh, it&#146;s wrong.", "answer": " stop it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": "  no! no! it&#146;s wrong! it&#146;s-it&#146;s-it&#146;s naughty. it&#146;s taboo.", "answer": " shut the book!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " so?!", "answer": " so?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " it&#146;s thursday! how was the audition?!", "answer": " wh? monday, one day. tuesday, two day. wednesday, when huh what? thurs&#151; oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}]